Register of the Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
1976-2008
2009C61
Hoover Institution Archives
124 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (53.1 linear feet)
The collection consists of circulated material, serial issues, bulletins, clippings, other printed matter, and notes relating to political parties and political leaders of post-Soviet Russia and other parts of the former Soviet Union. Used as research material for various publications by Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ.
Pribylovskiĭ, Vladimir, collector.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2009, with an increment received in 2010.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Vladimir Valerianovich Pribylovskiĭ was a Russian political analyst, journalist, and human rights activist. In the 1980s he was persecuted by Soviet authorities for spreading banned literature. Pribylovskiĭ emerged as an expert commentator in Russian political and journalistic circles in the early 1990s, after he co-founded a newspaper and a think tank, both called Panorama. He authored a series of "Who’s who" reference works on Russian politics. In 2005 he launched the Russian-language website Anticompromat.org, which is a collection of biographies of Russian politicians, compiled and written by Pribylovskiĭ from a variety of published sources. The site was included in the Russian Federal List of Extremist Materials. Pribylovskiĭ also authored more than 40 books. On January 13, 2016, Pribylovskiĭ was found dead in his Moscow apartment.
Scope and Content of Collection
The papers of Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ consist of circulated material, serial issues, bulletins, clippings, other printed matter, and published and unpublished writings. While working on his writings, Pribylovskiĭ collected material reflecting his interests in the social, political, and economic situation in the Soviet Union, post-Soviet Russia, and former Soviet republics. This material became the foundation for his political books and articles.
Arrangement Statement
The collection was arranged in files by Pribylovskiĭ, and his folder titles for research material have been retained. A typical file contains notes, articles, clippings, and other printed matter.
Russia (Federation)--Politics and government--1991-; Former Soviet republics--Politics and government.
- Analiticheskie tsentry, 1990-1996
  - General, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 69: 13-14, Box-folder 93: 19-20)
  - "Analiticheskii tsentr Russkogo obshchenatsional'nogo soiuza,", circa 1990 (Box-folder 69: 17)
  - "RF-politika,", 1992-1994 (Box-folder 69: 16)
  - "RAU-Korporatsiia (Rossiisko-amerikanskii universitet),", 1991-1993 (Box-folder 68: 13-14)
- Arbitrazhnye sudy Rossii, 1999 (Box-folder 101: 1-3)
- Armiia, 1996-2001
  - General, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 100: 4)
  - "Persony,", 1997-2000 (Box-folder 100: 5)
  - "Korruptsiia,", 1996-1997 (Box-folder 100: 6)
- Avtonomii Rossii: persony, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 67: 1-2)
- Biographical sources for Russian politicians, 1989-2006
  Scope and Contents note
  Consists of materials collected by Pribylovskii from a variety of published sources. Arranged alphabetically by personal name.
  - Abalkin, Leonid Ivanovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Abdulatipov, Ramazan Gadzhimuratovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Abramov, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Abramovich, Roman Arkad'evich, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Abrikosov, Aleksei Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Achalov, Vladislav Alekseevich, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Adamishin, Anatolii Leonidovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Adamkus, Valdas, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Adamov, Evgenii Olegovich, 1998 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Adamovich, Ales' Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Adarcheva, Liliia Stefanovna, 1996 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Adrov, Valerii Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Afanas'ev, Aleksandr, 1993 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Afanas'ev, Iurii Nikolaevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Afanas'ev, Mikhail, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Agafonov, Valentin Alekseevich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Aganbegian, Abel Gezovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Agapov, Boris Nikolaevich, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Agapova, Elena Viktorovna, 1996 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Aiatskov, Dmitrii Fedorovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Aivazian, Nikolai Vartanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Akaev, Askar Akaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Akhmetov, Rashit Rakipovich, 1991 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Akimov, Vladimir Vladimirovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Akporisov, Vasilii Vasil'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Aksenenko, Nikolai Emel'ianovich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Aksenov, Vasilii Pavlovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Aksiuchits, Viktor Vladimirovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Alekperov, Vagit Iusupovich, 1993 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Aleksandrov, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Aleksandrov, Aleksei Viktorovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Aleksandrov, Sergei Valer'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Aleksashenko, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Alekseev, Aleksandr Sergeevich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Alekseev, Sergei Sergeevich, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Alekseeva, Liudmila Mikhailovna, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Aliev, Geidar Alievich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Aliev, Il'kham Geidarovich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Aliev, Khasan Magomedovich, 1993 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Alksnis, Viktor Imantovich, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - Almazov, Sergei Nikolaevich, circa 1999 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Ambartsumov, Evgenii Arshakovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Ametistov, Ernest Mikhailovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Amirov, Said Dzhaparovich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Amonashvili, Shalva Aleksandrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Ananich, Vladimir Iulianovich, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andreev, Aleksandr, 1994 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andreev, Andrei Leonidovich, 1992 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andreev, Sergei Iur'evich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andreeva, Nina Aleksandrovna, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Andronov, Iona Ionovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Angelevich, Arkadii Vladimirovich, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anikiev, Anatolii Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anishchenko, Gleb Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anisimov, Stanislav Vasil'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anninskii, Lev Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anodina, Tat'iana Grigor'evna, 1996 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Anpilov, Viktor Ivanovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Antonov, Mikhail Fedorovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Aparina, Alevtina Viktorovna, 1996 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Arbatov, Aleksei Georgievich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Arbatov, Georgii Arkad'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Arkhipov, Andrei Viacheslavovich, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - Arnol'd, Vladimir Igorevich, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Aronov, Aleksandr Iakovlevich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Arsanov, Vakha, 1997 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Arsen'ev, Pavel, 1994 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Arsen'ev, Vladilen Vladilenovich, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Artemov, Igor' Vladimirovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Arzhannikov, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Ashin, Nikolai Iur'evich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Askerkhanov, Gamid Rashidovich, 1996 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Aslakhanov, Aslambek Akhmedovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Aslanidi, Aleksandr Valentinovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Asmolov, Aleksandr Grigor'evich, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Assekritov, Stanislav Vasil'evich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Astaf'ev, Mikhail Grigor'evich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Astaf'ev, Viktor Petrovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Astrakhankina, Tat'iana Aleksandrovna, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Atal'iants, Artem, Iur'evich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Aushev, Ruslan Sultanovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Auzanov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Avaliani, Teimuraz Georgievich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Avdiiskii, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Avelichev, Aleksandr Konstantinovich, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Aven, Petr Olegovich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Averintsev, Sergei Sergeevich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Averkiev, Igor' Valer'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Babaev, Vladimir Viktorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Babichev, Vladimir Stepanovich, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Babitskii, Andrei Maratovich, 2000 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Baburin, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Baglai, Marat Viktorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Bairamova, Fauzia Aukhadievna, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Bakatin, Vadim Viktorovich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Bakhmin, Viacheslav Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Baklanov, Oleg Dmitrievich, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Baluev, Vladislav, 1993 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Barannikov, Viktor Pavlovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Barchuk, Vasilii Vasil'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Barkashov, Aleksandr Petrovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Barsukov, Mikhail Ivanovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Baryshev, Vladimir Ivanovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Basaev, Shamil' Salmanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Bashmachnikov, Vladimir Fedorovich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Baskin, Il'ia Mikhailovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Batalov, Aleksei Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Batkin, Leonid Mikhailovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Batshev, Vladimir Semenovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Baturin, Iurii Mikhailovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Bauer, Vladimir Anatol'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Bek, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Bekh, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Bekhchanov, Iurii Vladimirovich, 1997 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Beklemishcheva, Ol'ga Alekseevna, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Beliaev, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Beliaev, Iurii Aleksandrovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Beliaev, Sergei Georgievich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Beliakov, Aleksandr Stepanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Belotserkovskii, Vadim, circa 1992 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Belov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Belov, Leonid Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Belov, Vasilii Ivanovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Belozertsev, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Bendukidze, Kakha Avtandilovich, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Berezovskii, Sergei Abramovich, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 3: 6-7)
  - Bespalov, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bessmertnykh, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Betaneli, Nugzar Iraklievich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bezlepkina, Liudmila Fedorovna, 1996 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bezrukov, Igor' Aleksandrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bezverkhii, Sergei Fedorovich, 1994 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bezverkhii, Viktor Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Bilenkov, Sergei Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Binkin, Boris, circa 1992 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Biriukova, Aleksandra Pavlovna, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Birman, Igor Iakovlevich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Blagovolin, Sergei Evgen'evich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Blokhin, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 2000 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Blokov, Ivan Pavlovich, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bobyshev, Dmitrii, 1996 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bocharov, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bochin, Leonid Arnol'dovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bochkarev, Vasilii Kuz'mich, 1999 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bogachev, Vladimir Valentinovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bogdanov, Vladimir Leonidovich, 1998 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bogdanov, Vsevolod Leonidovich, 1996 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Bogomolov, Oleg Timofeevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Bogoraz, Larisa Iosifovna, circa 1995 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Boiko, Maksim Vladimirovich, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Boiko, Oleg Viktorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Bokan', Iurii Ivanovich, 1994 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Bokser, Vladimir Oskarovich, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Boldin, Valerii Ivanovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Boldyrev, Iurii Iur'evich, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - Bolonkin, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Boltianskii, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Bol'shakov, Aleksei Alekseevich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Bol'shakov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1994 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Bondarenko, Iurii Konstantinovich, 1993 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Bondarenko, Vladimir Grigor'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Bonner, Elena Georgievna, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Boos, Georgii Valentinovich, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Bordiuzha, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Borodin, Oleg Petrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Borodin, Pavel Pavlovich, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Borovik, Artem Genrikhovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Borovoi, Konstantin Natanovich, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Borshchev, Valerii Vasil'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Bossert, Viktor Davydovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Bradwein, M., 1995 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Bragin, Viacheslav Ivanovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Braginskii, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Brevnov, Boris Anatol'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Brezhnev, Andrei Iur'evich, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Briachikhin, Aleksei Mikheevich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Brodskii (Brodsky), Iosif (Josef) Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Brumel', Aleksei Nikolaevich, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Bryntsalov, Vladimir Alekseevich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Bukharin, Kirill, 1994 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Bukovskii, Vladimir Konstantinovich, 1996 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Bulavinov, Vadim Evgen'evich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Bulgak, Vladimir Borisovich, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Bunin, Pavel Grigor'evich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - Burataeva, Aleksandra Mazhievna, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Buravlev, Konstantin Eduardovich, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Burbulis, Gennadii Eduardovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Burkov, Sergei Vasil'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Burkov, Valerii Anatol'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Burlakov, Matvei Prokop'evich, 1994 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Burliaev, Nikolai Petrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Bushuev, Vitalii Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Butov, Vladimir Iakovlevich, 1999 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Butusov, Kirill Mikhailovich, 1999 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Bychkov, Evgenii Matveevich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Bykov, Anatolii Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Bykov, Vasil' Vladimirovich, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Bystritskaia, Elina Avraamovna, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Bystritskii, Andrei Georgievich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Bystrov, Evgenii Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Chaika, Iurii Iakovlevich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Chaplygin, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1996 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Chebrikov, Viktor Mikhailovich, 1996 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Chechevatov, Viktor Stepanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Chelnokov, Mikhail Borisovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Chepurnoi, Andrei Gennad'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Cherepkov, Viktor Ivanovich, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Cherkesov, Viktor Vasil'evich, 2000 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Cherkizov, Andrei Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Chernavin, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Chernetskii, Arkadii Mikhailovich, 1999 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Chernetskii, Vladimir Nikolaevich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Chernichenko, Iurii Dmitrievich, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Chernogorodskii, Valerii Petrovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Chernogorov, Aleksandr Leonidovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Chernoivanov, Ivan Konstantinovich, 1995 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Chernomord, Petr Vasil'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - Chernomyrdin, Viktor Stepanovich, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 5: 3-4)
  - Chernyi, Lev Semenovich, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Chernyi, Mikhail Semenovich, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Chernyshev, Aleksei Andreevich, 2000 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Chilingarov, Artur Nikolaevich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Chimburov, Ivan Dmitrievich, 1993 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Chizhov, Sergei Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Chornovil, Viacheslav Maksimovich, 1996 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Chub, Vladimir Fedorovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Chubais, Anatolii Borisovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 5: 8-11)
  - Chubais, Igor' Borisovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Chuev, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 1990-2002 (Box-folder 5: 13-15)
  - Chukhin, Ivan Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Chumak, Alan Vladimirovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Chuprinin, Sergei Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Churilov, Valerii Andreevich, 1990 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Churkin, Vitalii Ivanovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Dal'skii, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1997 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Dam'e, Vadim Valer'evich, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Danilov, Gennadii Andreevich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Danilov, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Danilov-Danil'ian, Viktor Ivanovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Dashko, Iurii Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Davidenko, Georgii Mikhailovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Davitashvili, Dzhuna (Evgeniia) Iuvashevna, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Davituliani, Valentin Vladimirovich, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Davydov, Oleg Dmitrievich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Davydov, Viktor Fedorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Debrianskaia, Evgeniia, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Deinekin, Fedor Stepanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Deliagin, Mikhail Gennad'evich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Demin, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Demin, Iurii Georgievich, 1997 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Demin, Valerii Nikitovich, 1997 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Denisenko, Bella Anatol'evna, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Denisov, Aleksandr Vital'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Denisov, Anatolii Alekseevich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Deripaska, Oleg Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Derkovskii, Oleg Mikhailovich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Desiatov, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Dibrov, Dmitrii Alksandrovich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Diskin, Iosif Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Dmitriev, Mikhail Aronovich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Dmitriev, Sergei Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dmitriev, Viktor Vladimirovich, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dmitrieva, Oksana Genrikhovna, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dmitrieva, Tat'iana Borisovna, circa 1995 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dneprov, Eduard Dmitrievich, 1996 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dobrodeev, Oleg Borisovich, 1996 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Dodolev, Evgenii Iur'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Dogaev, Andrei Iur'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Dolgolaptev, Anatolii Vasil'evich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Domnina, Valentina Akesandrovna, circa 1995 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Donskoi, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 2006 (Box-folder 49: 7)
  - Dontsov, Sergei Evgen'evich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Dorenko, Segei Leonidovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Dornbush, Rudiger, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Doronina, Tat'iana Vasil'evna, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Dovgan', Vladimir Viktorovich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Draganov, Valerii Gavrilovich, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Drozdov, Aleksandr Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Druganov, Sergei Petrovich, 1990 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Druzenko, Anatolii Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Dubenetskii, Iakov Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Dubinin, Sergei Konstantinovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Dudaev, Dzhokhar Musaevich, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Dudinskii, Igor' Vikrtorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Dudnik, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dugin, Aleksandr Gel'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dunaev, Andrei Fedorovich, 1991 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dvornikov, Mikhail, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dvortsin, Mark Davidovich, 1992 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dzarasov, Soltan Safarbievich, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dzasokhov, Aleksandr Sergeevich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Dzhabrailov, Umar Alievich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Dzhemal', Geidar Dzhakhidovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Dzhugashvili, Galina Iakovlevna, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Dzoblaev, Shmidt Davydovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - D'iachenko, Tat'iana Borisovna, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - D'iakov, Sergei, 1993 (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Efimov, Vitalii Borisovich, 1996 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egiasarian, Ashot Gevorkovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egorov, Mikhail Konstantinovich, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egorov, Nikolai Dmitrievich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egorov, Sergei Efimovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egorov, Sergei Nesterovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Egorov, Vladimir Konstantinovich, 1999 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Elagin, Viacheslav, 1994 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - El'tsyn (Eltsyn), Boris Nikolaevich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 6: 12-15)
  - Emelin, Feliks Vladimirovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Emel'ianov, Aleksei Mikhailovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Emel'ianov, Valerii Nikolaevich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Emin, Vagan Gevorgovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Erin, Viktor Fedorovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Ernst, Lev Konstantinovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Erofeev, Viktor Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Esin, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evseev, Valerii Petrovich, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evstaf'ev, Anatolii, 1997 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evstigneev, Vladimir, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evtushenko, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evtushenko, Viktor, 1995 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Evtushenkov, Vladimir Petrovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Fadeev, Gennadii Mikhailovich, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Fadeev, Valerii Valer'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Fadin, Andrei Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Fal'ko, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Fateev, Valerii Petrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Fedorov, Aleksandr Mikhailovich (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Fedorov, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Fedorov, Boris Grigor'evich, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Fedorov, Boris Vladimirovich, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Fedorov, Igor' Igorevich, 1997 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Fedorov, Nikolai Vasil'evich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Fedorov, Sviatoslav Nikolaevich, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - Fedorov, Valentin Petrovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - Fedorov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - Fedoseev, Valerii, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 8)